

Dr.Eesha Munshi

Medical Project Manager

Contact

Address

Lucknow, India 226015

Phone

8155869682

E-mail

eeshamunshi01@gmail.com

Skills

Compliance skills

Negotiation skills

Team Player

Managing projects

Excellent communication skills

Inter-personal skills

Adaptable, dedicated and hardworking

Hardworking Consultant gifted at turning prospects into clients and delivering exceptional presentations. Engaging, personable and focused on delivering exemplary customer service. Outstanding motivator with adaptable communication style and success in collaborating across organizational levels. Having 2 years of professional experience in Account management, client relationship, consulting working for various healthcare clients in India and US Actively working for Indian Healthcare clients like Torrent pharmaceuticals, Baxter, Cochlear, Urgo Medicals, GSK pharmaceuticals. Well-trained and motivated to exceed expectations. Proven to bring results and work in fast-paced environments. Offers demonstrated strengths in building trust with clients and customers and has extensive healthcare career. Confident in approach and analytical in dealing with common problems. Handles emergencies with calm, level-headed mindset. Extensive management skills providing consulting, practice management solutions, process improvement.

Work History

2023-01 -Current

Medical Project Manager

Compendious Med Works, Lucknow

- Leading medical projects like designing, reviewing and drafting question bank on medical subjects.
- Research about latest advances in digital healthcare and writing articles on same.
- Coordinating with team for graphic designing and app development.
- Handling team of 4 members.
- Coordinating with clients and delivering meetings with them.

2022-08 -2023-01

Healthcare Consultant

Antal International, Lucknow

- Specialized in maintaining end to end recruiting process, sourcing, screening, interviewing candidates for medical devices and pharmaceuticals companies
- Worked for Indian Healthcare clients like Torrent pharmaceuticals, Baxter, Cochlear, Urgo Medicals, GSK pharmaceuticals
- Have experience in negotiation, client and candidate management

- Specialized in dealing with mid to senior level positions across healthcare industry
- Consulting and advising candidates
- Experience in preparing discreet, job chase lead and preparing qualifying job with clients

2020-11 -2021-12

Account Executive

Apidel Technogies, Lucknow

- Built and strengthened relationships with new and existing accounts to drive revenue growth.
- Strengthened customer relationships with proactive and collaborative approach to managing needs.
- In second closings and offer closings with candidates
- Resolved problems, improved operations and provided exceptional service
- Resolved conflicts and negotiated mutually beneficial agreements between parties
- Developed team communications and information for meetings
- Handled calls and email to address customer inquiries and concerns
- Completed paperwork, recognizing discrepancies and promptly addressing for resolution
- Participated in continuous improvement by generating suggestions, engaging in problem solving activities to support teamwork
- Led projects and analyzed data to identify opportunities for improvement
- Improved operations through consistent hard work and dedication
- Participated in team-building activities to enhance working relationships.

2020-05 -2020-11

Healthcare Management Executive

The Aligner Company, Vadodara

- Resolved problems, improved operations and provided exceptional service.
 - Resolved conflicts and negotiated mutually beneficial agreements between parties.
 - Developed team communications and information for meetings. Handled calls and email to address customer inquiries and

concerns.

- Completed paperwork, recognizing discrepancies and promptly addressing for resolution.
- Participated in continuous improvement by generating suggestions, engaging in problem solving activities to support teamwork.
- Led projects and analyzed data to identify opportunities for improvement.
- Improved operations through consistent hard work and dedication. Participated in team-building activities to enhance working relationships.

Education

2018-08 - MBA
2020-06 Navrachna University - Vadodara, GJ

2012-08 - Bachelors of Dental Surgery
2017-01 KMS Dental College And Hospital - Vadodara, GJ